lonak.com 2017-10-24

# Lonak - سیاست حفظ اسرار

**  
Lonak privacy policy**

This Privacy Policy describes Lonak's policies and procedures on the collection, use and disclosure of your information. Lonak receives your information through our various web sites, SMS, APIs, services and third-parties ("Services"). When using any of our Services you consent to the collection, transfer, manipulation, storage, disclosure and other uses of your information as described in this Privacy Policy. Irrespective of which country that you reside in or create information from, your information may be used by Lonak all countries.

Information Collection and Use

**Information Collected Upon Registration:** When you create or reconfigure a Lonak account, you provide some institutional and personal information, such as your name, company name, tax number, username, password, and email address. Some of this information, for example, your name, company name, tax number, phone number, fax , is listed publicly on our Services, including on your profile page and in search results. Some Services, such as search, public user profiles and viewing lists, do not require registration.

**Log Data:** Our servers automatically record information ("Log Data") created by your use of the Services. Log Data may include information such as your IP address, browser type, the referring domain, pages visited, and search terms. Other actions, such as interactions with advertisements, may also be included in Log Data.

**Demands, Announcements, Lists and other Public Information:** Our Services are primarily designed to help you share information with the world. Most of the information you provide to us is information you are asking us to make public.. Our default is almost always to make the information you provide. Your public information is broadly and instantly disseminated. For example, announcements and profile are searchable by many search engines and are immediately delivered via e-mail and our APIs to a wide range of users and services. You should be careful about all information that will be made public by Lonak, not just your announcements.  

Information Sharing and Disclosure

**Your Consent:** We may share or disclose your information with your consent, such as when you use a third party web client to access your Lonak account.

**Service Providers:** We engage certain trusted third parties to perform functions and provide services to us. We may share your personal information with these third parties, but only to the extent necessary to perform these functions and provide such services, and only pursuant to obligations mirroring the protections of this privacy policy.

**Law and Harm:** We may disclose your information if we believe that it is reasonably necessary to comply with a law, regulation or legal request; to protect the safety of any person or company; to address fraud, security or technical issues, fraudulent issues; or to protect Lonak’s rights or property.

**Business Transfers:** In the event that Lonak is involved in a bankruptcy, merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets, your information may be sold or transferred as part of that transaction. The promises in this privacy policy will apply to your information as transferred to the new entity.

**Non-Private or Non-Personal Information:** We may share or disclose your non- private information, such as your public messages, products, services, contact information.

Modifying Your Information

If you are a registered user of our Services, we provide you with tools to access or modify the information you provided to us and associated with your account.

Changes to this Policy

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. The most current version of the policy will govern our use of your information and will always be at http://www.lonak.com/privacy.asp. If we make a change to this policy that, in our sole discretion, is material, we will notify you via an e-mail to the email associated with your account. By continuing to access or use the Services after those changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy.
